Guide to the Garden Information Center of Ithaca records, 1958-1973
Garden Information Center of Ithaca records, 1958-1973
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Garden Information Center of Ithaca records, 1958-1973.
3685
Garden Information Center of Ithaca.
1.5 cubic ft.
Scrapbooks, correspondence, minutes, newspaper clippings, an organizational history, membership lists, annual reports, a constitution, and bylaws.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes scrapbooks, correspondence, minutes, and newspaper clippings related to various projects, and to the annual plant sale; also organization history, membership lists, annual reports, constitution and bylaws.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes scrapbooks, correspondence, minutes, and newspaper clippings related to various projects, and to the annual plant sale; also organization history, membership lists, annual reports, constitution and bylaws.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Garden Information Center of Ithaca.
Subjects:
Horticulture.
Places:
Ithaca (N.Y.).; Tompkins County (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.; Minutes (administrative records); Constitutions.; Bylaws (administrative records)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Florence Hoard's file, 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Constitution, by-laws, 1957-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Corresponding secretary, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Membership, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- L.H. MacDaniels, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Annual meeting, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Newsletters, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Planters and window boxes, project for Ithaca, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Annual reports, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Traffic circle roses, Oak Ave., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- DeWitt Park rose planting, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Annual reports, to 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Cornell Infirmary rose planting, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Minutes for historian, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Insurance, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Corresponding secretary, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Constitution, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Additional papers, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Additional papers, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- List of all members, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Plant sale, 1958-1963 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Plant sale, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Plant sale, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Plant sale, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Plant sale, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Plant sale, co-chairman report, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Plant sale, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Properties Committee (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 13)
- History material (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Cooperative Extension newsletters, ca. 1957-1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Roses (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Horticulture (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Pot pourri (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Christmas window boxes (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Scrapbook, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Scrapbook, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
- Scrapbook, 1960-1963 (Box 4)
- Scrapbook, 1964-1968 (Box 4)